<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Quakes NZ</string>
    <string name="magnitude">Magnitude: %1$.1f</string>
    <string name="depth">Depth: %1$.0f km</string>
    <string name="location">%1$d km away from %2$s</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_body">Quakes NZ was built in Wellington, New Zealand by Leandro Peralta and Daniel Watts.\n\nLeandro Peralta - Developer\nleandro.peralta@androideas.net\n\nDaniel Watts - Designer\ndaniel@wattscreative.me</string>
    <string name="acknowledgements">Acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="acknowledgements_body">We would like to thank the following organisations for providing the awesome data used within this app.\n\ngeonet.org.nz\nThe New Zealand GeoNet project and its sponsors EQC, GNS Science and LINZ.\n\ncivildefence.govt.nz\nThe Ministry of Civil Defence and Emergency Management.</string>
    <string name="before_title">Before an Earthquake</string>
    <string name="before_body">Getting ready before an earthquake strikes will help reduce damage to your home and business and help you survive.\n\nDevelop a Household Emergency Plan. Assemble and maintain your emergency survival Items for your home and workplace, as well as a portable getaway kit.\n\nPractice Drop, Cover and Hold.\n\nIdentify safe places within your home, school or workplace. See the right-hand panel for more information about safe places.\n\nCheck your household insurance policy for cover and amount.\n\nSeek qualified advice to make sure your house is secured to its foundations and ensure any renovations comply with the New Zealand Building Code.\n\nSecure heavy items of furniture to the floor or wall.\n\nVisit www.eqc.govt.nz to find out how to quake-safe your home.</string>
    <string name="during_title">During an Earthquake</string>
    <string name="during_body">If you are inside a building, move no more than a few steps, drop, cover and hold. Stay indoors till the shaking stops and you are sure it is safe to exit. In most buildings in New Zealand you are safer if you stay where you are until the shaking stops.\n\nIf you are in an elevator, drop, cover and hold. When the shaking stops, try and get out at the nearest floor if you can safely do so.\n\nIf you are outdoors when the shaking starts, move no more than a few steps away from buildings, trees, streetlights, and power lines, then Drop, Cover and Hold.\n\nIf you are at the beach or near the coast, drop, cover and hold then move to higher ground immediately in case a tsunami follows the quake.\n\nIf you are driving, pull over to a clear location, stop and stay there with your seatbelt fastened until the shaking stops. Once the shaking stops, proceed with caution and avoid bridges or ramps that might have been damaged.\n\nIf you are in a mountainous area or near unstable slopes or cliffs, be alert for falling debris or landslides.</string>
    <string name="after_title">After an Earthquake</string>
    <string name="after_body">Listen to your local radio stations as emergency management officials will be broadcasting the most appropriate advice for your community and situation.\n\nExpect to feel aftershocks.\n\nCheck yourself for injuries and get first aid if necessary. Help others if you can.\n\nBe aware that electricity supply could be cut, and fire alarms and sprinkler systems can go off in buildings during an earthquake even if there is no fire. Check for, and extinguish, small fires.\n\nIf you are in a damaged building, try to get outside and find a safe, open place. Use the stairs, not the elevators.\n\nWatch out for fallen power lines or broken gas lines, and stay out of damaged areas.\n\nOnly use the phone for short essential calls to keep the lines clear for emergency calls.\n\nIf you smell gas or hear a blowing or hissing noise, open a window, get everyone out quickly and turn off the gas if you can. If you see sparks, broken wires or evidence of electrical system damage, turn off the electricity at the main fuse box if it is safe to do so.\n\nKeep your animals under your direct control as they can become disorientated. Take measures to protect your animals from hazards, and to protect other people from your animals.\n\nIf your property is damaged, take notes and photographs for insurance purposes. If you rent your property, contact your landlord and your contents insurance company as soon as possible.</string>
    <string name="emergency_advice">Emergency Advice</string>
    <string name="before">Before</string>
    <string name="during">During</string>
    <string name="after">After</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="transition_name" translatable="false">list_to_detail</string>
    <string name="no_data_available">No data available</string>
    <string name="quake_details">Quake Details</string>
    <string name="failed_to_download">Failed to download latest quakes data.</string>
    <string name="intensity">Intensity</string>
    <string name="select_intensity">Select Intensity</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="intensity_pref_summary">%s and above</string>
    <string name="unnoticeable">Unnoticeable</string>
    <string name="weak">Weak</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="moderate">Moderate</string>
    <string name="strong">Strong</string>
    <string name="severe">Severe</string>
    <string name="filter_view_quake_details">View Quake Details</string>
    <string name="default_share_content">A %1$s earthquake of magnitude %2$.1f occurred %3$s. #QuakesNZ http://www.geonet.org.nz/quakes/region/newzealand/%4$s</string>
    <string name="error_loading_feature">Failed to load quake details.</string>
</resources>